# **Bui Chi Trung**

Location: Ha Noi, Viet Nam

Email: trungcspntl@gmail.com | Mobile: +84-0988864538 LinkedIn | GitHub

#### SOFTWARE ENGINEER

I am a software engineer with over 2 years of experience. I have worked with various languages including **Go**, Python, PHP, and JavaScript. I have experience in managing large-scale projects and optimizing processes for parallel execution across multiple threads and nodes. My expertise extends to both REST and **gRPC** APIs.

### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **GPU Software Engineer**

Moreh

December 2023 – Present Ha Noi, Viet Nam

- Utilizing components of GPUs specialized for AI applications to implement and optimize various artificial neural network layers using CUDA, HIP.
- Parallelized AI model inference process using multiple threads, multiple GPUs, including GPUs distributed across different nodes, utilizing various techniques such as data parallelism and pipeline parallelism,...
- Project: Optimize an inference serving system with Llama-2 using multiple GPUs. Achieved throughput on 13 billion parameters model: **245 tokens/s**, equal to the state-of-the-art library for LLM inference vLLM.
- · Obtained skills: C++, CUDA, HIP

**Backend Developer** 

Aug 2022 – December 2023 Ha Noi, Viet Nam

Teko Viet Nam

- Fork <u>Superset</u>, an open-source platform for data exploration and visualization to customize authentication and authorization using Single Sign-On (SSO) flow. This enables seamless integration of Superset into Teko products.
- Develop and operate a service that stores data for over **50 million** users, capturing details such as transaction amounts and their most recent transactions, along with their online behavior including page views and interactions with commercial banners in **nearly real-time**. Leveraging this data, we automatically categorize customers and implement tailored marketing campaigns for each customer segment.
- Obtained skills: Go, gRPC, Microservices, Column-oriented database, React.

**DevOps Internship** 

Apr 2022 – Jun 2022

Worldquant

Ha Noi, Viet Nam

- Develop a service that controls google cloud platform instances used to execute quantive algorithms.
- · Obtained skills: Python, Linux.

## **EDUCATION**

## **University of Engineer and Technology**

Major: Infomation Technology. GPA: 3,84

Jul 2019 – Sep 2023 Ha Noi, Viet Nam

774 7701, 770

**Programming**: Fourth prize in Vietnam National Olympiad in Informatics - VNOI 2018

**English** : 900 TOEIC, 7.5 VSTEP

## **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

**Languages** : Golang, C++, Java, Javascript, Python, PHP.

**Frameworks**: React.js, Vue, Laravel, Flask.

**Databases** : MySQL, Redis.

**Dev Tools** : gRPC, Docker, Git, Grafana.

#### **PROJECTS**

## **Personal project**

Golang, Redis, PostgreSQL.

Source Code

A custom plugin that can be integrated with Kong API Gateway to parse, build the Abstract Syntax Tree then cache GraphQL request routing through Kong API Gateway using Redis. Prometheus & Loki are integrated to manage the plugin state and log.